<?xml version="1.0"?>
<object>
  <property name="accept-on-click">True</property>

  <cookie_consent_configuration>
      <object>
        <property name="lang">it</property>
        <property name="text">
            Per offrire informazioni e servizi nel miglior modo possibile, questo sito utilizza cookie tecnici e cookie di terza parte.
            Per maggiori informazioni sui cookie utilizzati e su come eventualmente disabilitarli leggi la nostra $privacy_link.
        </property>
        <property name="privacy-link-url">/privacy</property>
        <property name="privacy-link-text">privacy policy</property>
        <property name="dashboard-link-text"></property>
      </object>
      <object>
        <property name="lang">en</property>
        <property name="text">
            This site uses technical and third-party cookie to provide better informations and services.
            If you want to know more or how to disable them, read our $privacy_link.
        </property>
        <property name="privacy-link-url">/en/privacy</property>
        <property name="privacy-link-text">privacy policy</property>
        <property name="dashboard-link-text"></property>
      </object>
  </cookie_consent_configuration>

  <optout_configuration>
      <!-- this configuration is related to sc.social.like >= 2.3 -->
    <object>
        <property name="app-id">social</property>
        <property name="cookies">
            <element>social</element>
        </property>
        <property name="default-value">true</property>
        <optout_configuration_ui>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">it</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookie di condivisione con i social network</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Cookie di terze parti legati all'uso di plug-in di social network per la condivisione dei contenuti di questo sito.
					Senza questi cookie non si vede quante condivisioni di un contenuto sono state fatte dagli altri utenti.
                </property>
            </object>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">en</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookies shared with social networks</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Third-party cookies joined with social network's plugins for sharing content of such websites.
					Such cookies are mandatory to determine how many times content has been shared by other users.
                </property>
            </object>
        </optout_configuration_ui>
    </object>
    <!-- this configuration is related to Products.Maps >= 3.4 -->
    <object>
        <property name="app-id">maps</property>
        <property name="cookies">
            <element>maps</element>
        </property>
        <property name="default-value">true</property>
        <optout_configuration_ui>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">it</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookie di Google Maps</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Cookie di terze parti legati all'uso di plug-in per la visualizzazione di mappe realizzate con Google Maps.
					Senza questi cookie non verranno visualizzate tali mappe e la relativa posizione dei contenuti georeferenziati. 
                </property>
            </object>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">en</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookies of Google Maps</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Third-party cookies joined with Google Maps plugins.
					Such cookies are mandatory for map's rendering and georeferencing of items therein. 
                </property>
            </object>
        </optout_configuration_ui>
    </object>
    <!-- this configuration is related to collective.analyticspanel >= 0.5.0 -->
    <object>
        <property name="app-id">analytics</property>
        <property name="cookies">
            <element>analytics</element>
        </property>
        <property name="default-value">false</property>
        <optout_configuration_ui>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">it</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookie analytics</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Analoghi ai cookie tecnici, sono usati solo dal gestore del sito per finalità statistiche e di monitoraggio e non consentono l'identificazione dell'utente.
                    Senza questi cookie non cambia nulla nell'utilizzo del sito ma si impedisce al gestore di analizzare le prestazioni e l'esperienza di navigazione dell'utente.
                </property>
            </object>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">en</property>
                <property name="app-title">Analytics cookies</property>
                <property name="app-description">
					As for technical cookies, analytics cookies are exclusively used by webmasters for statistical and monitoring purposes, and do not allow for user identification.
					Such cookies do not modify the general website usage, but are needed by webmasters to analyze the website performances and to evaluate the user experience.
                </property>
            </object>
        </optout_configuration_ui>
    </object>
    <!-- this configuration is related to some redturtle.video extensions -->
    <object>
        <property name="app-id">video</property>
        <property name="cookies">
            <element>video</element>
        </property>
        <property name="default-value">true</property>
        <optout_configuration_ui>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">it</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookie di piattaforme video</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Cookie di terze parti legati all'uso di plug-in per la visualizzazione di video su piattaforme esterne (es. YouTube).
                    Senza questi cookie non possiamo mostrare i video all'interno del sito; ove possibile il video è sostituito da un link alla piattaforma esterna ove risiede. 
                </property>
            </object>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">en</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookies of web video platforms</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Third-party cookies joined with web video platforms (i.e. Youtube).
					Such cookies are mandatory for playing videos within websites; if possible, videos are substituted by links to the external web video platform they belong to. 
                </property>
            </object>
        </optout_configuration_ui>
    </object>
    <!-- this configuration requires rer.consentembed -->
    <object>
        <property name="app-id">embed</property>
        <property name="cookies">
            <element>embed</element>
        </property>
        <property name="default-value">true</property>
        <optout_configuration_ui>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">it</property>
                <property name="app-title">Cookie di embed da siti esterni</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Cookie di terze parti legati all'inclusione di codice proveniente da siti esterni (es. inclusione di news da Facebook o Twitter).
                    Senza questi cookie non verrà visualizzato il contenuto proveniente dal sito esterno.
                </property>
            </object>
            <object>
                <property name="lang">en</property>
                <property name="app-title">Embed cookies from external websites</property>
                <property name="app-description">
                    Third-party cookies joined with code of external websites (i.e. news inclusion from Facebook or Twitter).
					Such cookies are mandatory to visualize content from external websites.
                </property>
            </object>
        </optout_configuration_ui>
    </object>
  </optout_configuration>

</object>